Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company Selected Personnel Files 5295
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series 2: Subject Files, 1901-1969
  - Claims [folder 4 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2d)
  - Claims [folder 5 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2e)
  - Claims [folder 6 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2f)
  - Claims [folder 7 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2g)
  - Claims [folder 8 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2h)
  - Claims [folder 9 of 9], 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2i)
  - Claims [folder 1 of 3], 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1a)
  - Claims [folder 2 of 3], 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1b)
  - Claims [folder 3 of 3], 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1c)
  - Claims [folder 1 of 3], 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2a)
  - Claims [folder 2 of 3], 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2b)
  - Claims [folder 3 of 3], 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2c)
  - Claims, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Claims, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Conference between Committees Representing Railroads and Labor Organization, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Costs - Operating, repairs, equipment, etc. [folder 1 of 3], 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 6a)
  - Costs - Operating, repairs, equipment, etc. [folder 2 of 3], 1938-1949 (Box 7, Folder 6b)
  - Costs - Operating, repairs, equipment, etc. [folder 3 of 3], 1945-1950 (Box 7, Folder 6c)
  - Court Pay - for Employees Attending Court, 1925-1939 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Death and Illness of Employees, 1941-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Death records of ICRR employees, reports on accidents that caused death or injury, condolences sent by ICRR, and get well soon letters sent by ICRR
  - Diesel Engines, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dining Car Service - Rates of Pay, 1921-1933 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Discipline - Applying Records System to employees Covered by Clerks' Agreement, 1925-1937 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Discipline - Assessment of, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Discipline - General (Closed), 1902-1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    August 1902 to February 1920
  - Discipline - General (Closed), 1922-1942 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Discipline - General, Requests from local chairman, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Discipline - Information to and from other roads, 1920-1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Discipline - Investigations, 1929-1944 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Discipline - Investigations, 1940-1945 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Discipline - Safety Rules, 1931-1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Discipline - Violations by firemen, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Discrimination - Association of Colored Railway Trainmen, 1920-1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Discrimination - African-American Employees, Train and Engine Service, Kentucky Div., Thomas D. Redd, 1919-1934 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination - African-American Firemen, Louisville and Evansville Districts, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 13a)
  - Discrimination - African-American Switchmen, Memphis, TN, 1927-1937 (Box 8, Folder 13b)
    1927: date of a conference, but all notes missing from file 1937: correspondence re African-American switchman Albert Pryor's attempt to organize fellow African-American switchmen
  - Discrimination - Mistreatment of African-American Employees, Investigation by Federal Coordinator, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Federal investigation of transportation prompted ICRR to document the number of African-Americans they employed and what workplace discrimination they faced. Also found in this folder is a memorandum, attached to a letter dated May 9, 1934, recording a narrative of the shootings of African-American employees (see also box 8, folders 23A-29 for additional documentation of these events).
  - Discrimination - National Association of Colored Locomotive Firemen, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Discrimination - African-American Brakeman, use of, Owensboro District, 1924-1939 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Discrimination - Number of African-American trainmen on IC System, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Discrimination - Fireman Maddox in re increase in Rate of Pay for African-American firemen, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Discrimination - African-American firemen, Vicksburg Route Division, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Discrimination - African-American trainmen on Kentucky Div., filing petition for Writ of Mandamus, 1932-1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    to compel the NRAB to hear complaint of Louisville Lodge #10, Association of Colored Railway Trainmen vs. Illinois Central Railroad Company
  - Discrimination - Seniority rule as between white and African-American firemen, 1924-1941 (Box 8, Folder 21a)
  - Discrimination - Seniority rights of Gilbert Clayborne, switchman, Memphis TN, 1935-1939 (Box 8, Folder 21b)
    Correspondence to and from George E. Washington, Mr. Clayborne's representative. (see box 18, folder 5 for additional materials on this case).
  - Discrimination - Seniority rights of African-American switchmen and brakemen; suits of various employees [folder 1 of 2], 1925-1941 (Box 8, Folder 22a)
  - Discrimination - Seniority rights of African-American switchmen and brakemen; suits of various employees [folder 2 of 2], 1925-1941 (Box 8, Folder 22b)
  - Discrimination - Internal report on intimidation of, violence against, and murder of African-American employees [folder 1 of 2], 1934 (Box 8, Folder 23a)
    Includes different drafts of report and memoranda describing conditions faced by African-American employees. The names of the victims are included in lists made during the three waves of violence in 1916, 1921-1922, and 1932-1933.
  - Discrimination - Shootings of African-American employees, Louisiana division, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 23b)
    Partial correspondence file of Chief Special Agent T. T. Keliher
  - Discrimination - Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith, 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    These two white ICRR trainmen were arrested for, confessed to, and tried for the murders and attempted murders of African-American ICRR trainmen in Jackson, Mississippi. They were found not guilty in a jury trial, and then sued the ICRR for back-pay, slander, and wrongful termination. Folder contains a memorandum, dated July 22, 1937, that contains the entire narrative of the shootings.
  - Discrimination - Reinstatement of Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith [1 of 5], 1934-1937 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, legal proceedings, court filings, and memoranda
  - Discrimination - Reinstatement of Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith [2 of 5], 1938 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Discrimination - Reinstatement of Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith [3 of 5], 1938 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Complete case file presented to National Railroad Adjustment Board; carrier exhibits include the confessions of Lee and Smith as well as portions of their criminal cases.
  - Discrimination - Reinstatement of Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith [4 of 5], 1939-1942 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, legal proceedings, court filings, and memoranda. Includes decision of Arbitration Board, which reinstated Smith and awarded him back-pay but denied Lee's claims.
  - Discrimination - Reinstatement of Reatie Lee and Emmett Smith [4 of 5], 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Account ledger sheets documenting monetary award to Smith from ICRR
  - Dues, non-payment of, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Efficiency Record Cards, entries on, 1910-1930 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Eight-Hour Movement, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    "Train and Enginemen: Eight hour movement, year 1916. Printed matter and miscellaneous circulars."
  - Employees - General, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    "Information re employees working conditions, etc. Commissioner of Labor Statistics, U.S. Department of Labor, 1935." "List of employee representatives residing in various States, 1936."
  - Employment Stabilization Program, Files 1 and 3, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    War Manpower Commission
  - Employment Stabilization Program, File 2 [folder 1 of 2], 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 5a)
  - Employment Stabilization Program, File 2 [folder 2 of 2], 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 5b)
  - Employment of Student Brakemen, Firemen, etc., 1940-1951 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Equipment, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Federated Order of Railroad Employees, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Fight for Freedom" comic book, 1950-1952 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Anti-communism, pro-America Red Scare era comic book with correspondence to all ICRR employees who were given a copy by management
  - "Foreman Talks to Foremen" by J. J. Phillips, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    magazine article from American Machinist
  - 40-Hour Work Week - Clerks, 1949-1953 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 40-Hour Work Week - Firemen and Oilers, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 40-Hour Work Week - General, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 40-Hour Work Week - Raise in Pay, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 40-Hour Work Week - Skilled Crafts, 1949-1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Fifty Year Veterans (of ICRR) - Dinners, Gold Passes, etc. [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1946 (Box 9, Folder 16a)
    contains list of each year's honorees, in addition to correspondence and programs from the Gold Pass Luncheon celebrations
  - Fifty Year Veterans (of ICRR) - Dinners, Gold Passes, etc. [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1946 (Box 9, Folder 16b)
  - Freight Handlers - Chicago - Demands, Agreements, etc., 1902-1905 (Box 10, Folder 1a)
  - Freight House Clerks - Chicago - Demands, 1903 (Box 10, Folder 1b)
  - Freight Handlers - Strike, May-June, 1912 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Freight Handlers - Strike, May-June 1912 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Freight Handlers - Strike, May-June, 1912 - Schedule Matters and Demands, 1910-1913 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Freight Handlers - Various Points - Schedules and Demands, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Freight Handlers - Various Points - Schedules and Demands, 1914-1915 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Freight Handlers - Various Points - Schedules and Demands, 1915-1919 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Freight Handlers - Schedule Demands - Various Points: Chicago, New Orleans, E. St. Louis, etc., 1906-1911 (Box 10, Folder 8a)
  - Freight Handlers - Rules - Chicago, Illinois, 1907-1910 (Box 10, Folder 8b)
  - Freight Handlers - Schedule Matters and Demands [folder 1 of 2], 1911-1913 (Box 10, Folder 9a)
  - Freight Handlers - Schedule Matters and Demands [folder 2 of 2], 1911-1913 (Box 10, Folder 9b)
  - Grievance(s), 1929-1932 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Delay in handling of, 1932 Manner in which they should be handled, 1929
  - Harriman Memorial Medals - Safety Awards [folder 1 of 2], 1917-1938 (Box 10, Folder 11a)
    given out by the American Museum of Safety
  - Harriman Memorial Medals - Safety Awards [folder 2 of 2], 1917-1938 (Box 10, Folder 11b)
  - Hours of Work - General, 1942-1951 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Howell-Barkley Bill, 1924-1925 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    To provide for settlement of disputes between carriers and their employees
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Co., 1929 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Request for information on rates of pay of certain groups of employees.
  - Illinois Central Magazine, 1942-1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    In addition to correspondence regarding the magazine, this folder includes a b&w photo of Corporal Genevieve Wade, WAAC, March 30, 1943, employee of the ICRR.
  - Japanese Government Railways, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Working conditions of employees; request for copies of our working agreements
  - Jurisdictional Dispute, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    between machinists and blacksmiths
  - Jurisdictional Dispute(s), 1948 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    between machinists and boilermakers; between blacksmiths and carmen
  - Jurisdictional Dispute(s), 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    between machinists and electricians; between machinists and blacksmiths
  - Jurisdictional Dispute(s), 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute(s), 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Jurisdictional Dispute(s), 1948-1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    between machinists and boilermakers
  - Labor Matters - General [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1955 (Box 11, Folder 10a)
    Numerous clippings and articles from various labor publications and major newspapers.
  - Labor Matters - General [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1955 (Box 11, Folder 10b)
  - Labor Matters - General [folder 1 of 2], 1940-1945 (Box 11, Folder 11a)
  - Labor Matters - General [folder 2 of 2], 1940-1945 (Box 11, Folder 11b)
    Folder includes a copy of "Railroad Notes" from November 1941, which has an article of intimidation, harassment, and disenfranchisement of African-American railroad firemen.
  - Labor Problems, Study by the Federal Coordinator, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 12a)
    "A Survey of the Rules Governing Wage Payments in Railroad Train and Engine Service" by the Federal Coordinator of Transportation, Section of Labor Relations
  - Labor Problems, Study of, by the Federal Coordinator, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 12b)
    (see also box 8, folder 12)
  - Labor Relations, information re, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Correspondence with W. H. Werner from Shreveport, Louisiana
  - Legislation, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Correspondence with Pennsylvania Railroad's Personnel Manager re a piece of legislation in new Jersey regarding crew consist.
  - Local Officers - Committee Elections, 1935-1940 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Lists of election results and list of committee members for shop crafts
  - Local Officers - Committee Elections, 1934-1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Local Officers - Committee Elections, 1935-1937 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Correspondence re rail passes for elected committee members
  - Longshoremen - General, 1921-1936 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Majority of records about 1923 strike in New Orleans
  - Lunch Periods, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Maintenance of Way Time Rolls, 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Marine Employees - rules, working conditions, wages in 1930, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Mexico - National Railways of, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    copies of agreements with labor organizations furnished
  - National League of Commission Merchants, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Information re wage matters
  - National Mediation Board, 1934-1947 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - National Mediation Board, 1940-1943 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Mediation Board, 1940-1943 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board, 1934-1940 (Box 12, Folder 5a)
  - National Mediation Board, 1953-1963 (Box 12, Folder 5b)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board [folder 1 of 2], 1934-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6a)
    Cases to be heard before the Board, etc.
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board [folder 2 of 2], 1934-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6b)
    Agreements covering Rates of Pay, Rules, and Working Conditions
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1939-1948 (Box 12, Folder 6c)
  - National Union of Railway Trackmen, 1901-1917 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National War Labor Board - Establishment of, 1942-1947 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Negotiation Procedures, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Oh Say Does That Star Spangled Banner Yet Wave" pamphlet, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Red scare era anti-communist pamphlet ordered for employees
  - Parlor Car Porters - Seniority, duties, etc., 1923-1934 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Wage rates, petition for raises, correspondence regarding who is the direct superior of these employee (warning: letters contain racial slurs).
  - Payroll Deductions - General, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    For war effort.
  - Pension Matters - General, 1941-1943 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Personnel - General, 1941-1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Contains org chart for filing grievances in 1941
  - Personnel - General, 1941-1948 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Force of office of manager of personnel.
  - Personnel - General, 1944-1955 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Employees -- indebtedness of
  - Pullman Equipment - Purchase of, 1945-1950 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Leasing and purchase of Pullman Cars; uniform contract with Pullman Company; servicing of Pullman Cars by railroad.
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Information re Seniority, Schedules etc., 1939-1946 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Separated by Groups: Clerks, 1939-1943; Maintenance of Way employees, 1940-1944; Engineers, 1941-1946; Conductors, suburban service, Chicago, 1941; Conductors, 1939-1945.
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Information re Seniority, Schedules etc., 1939-1945 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Separated by Groups: Shop crafts, skilled, 1939-1945; Firemen, 1938-1941; Vicksburg route firemen, 1941; Trainmen, 1940-1944.
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Information re Seniority, Schedules etc., 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Separated by Groups: Shop crafts, unskilled, 1938-1941; Suburban trainmen, 1941; Switchmen and switchtenders, 1941; Yardmen and switchmen, 1938-1941; Signal department employees, 1941; System Federation No. 99, 1941.
  - Railroad Retirement Board - Information re Seniority, Schedules etc., 1938-1947 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Separated by Groups: Telegraphers, 1939- 1944; Train porters, 1940; general, 1938-1943; Train dispatchers, 1938-1947; records of employees, 1941.
  - Railway Business Association, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    correspondence re "Railways and Organized Labor" by P. Harvey Middleton.
  - Railway Clerks Union - requests and decisions, 1904-1912 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    includes records re 1906 clerks' strike, including newspaper clippings.
  - Railway Labor Act [folder 1 of 2], 1926-1947 (Box 12, Folder 24a)
    Watson-Parker Railway Labor Act
  - Railway Labor Act [folder 2 of 2], 1926-1947 (Box 12, Folder 24b)
  - Railway Labor Act - posting notices of RLA only, 1944-1951 (Box 12, Folder 24c)
  - Railway Labor Act - litigation regarding, 1935-1948 (Box 12, Folder 24d)
  - Rates of Pay - Blacksmiths, 1943-1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Rates of Pay - Carmen, 1943-1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Rates of Pay - Clerical, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rates of Pay - African-American Firemen, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Rates of Pay - Engineers, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rates of Pay - Firemen and Oilers, 1937-1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rates of Pay - Firemen and Oilers, 1937-1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rates of Pay - Firemen and Oilers, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rates of Pay - General, 1921-1922 (Box 13, Folder 9a)
    (oversize charts are fragile)
  - Rates of Pay - General, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 9b)
  - Rates of Pay - System Federation No. 99, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 10a)
  - Rates of Pay - General, 1921-1922 (Box 13, Folder 10b)
  - Rates of Pay - Power Plant Employees and Shop Laborers, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    in Mechanical Department as of March 1, 1942
  - Rates of Pay - Power Plant Employees and Shop Laborers, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    in Mechanical Department as of December 27, 1943
  - Rates of Pay - Power Plant Employees and Shop Laborers, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    in Mechanical Department as of May 27, 1946
  - Rates of Pay - Power Plant Employees and Shop Laborers, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Reduction of Forces, 1938-1949 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Relief - implementation of 40 hour work week, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Representation - employee ballots and vote tallies, 1920-1921 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Union selection ballots and vote tallies
  - Representation - employee ballots and vote tallies, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Representation - ballots, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence re article "President Ryan on New Railway Labor Act", 1926 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Rules and rates of pay in train and yard service on the principle railroads of the United States, Canada, and Mexico", 1900 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rules, 1942-1947 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rules, 1905-1947 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Rules, 1945-1948 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rules, 1930-1937 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Sabotage during wartime, 1941-1943 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Shiftwork [folder 1 of 2], 1941-1948 (Box 14, Folder 7a)
  - Shiftwork [folder 2 of 2], 1941-1948 (Box 14, Folder 7b)
  - Signal Department, 1934-1936 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Socialism - subversive activities, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Red Scare era pamphlets and publications from House Un-American Committee
  - Strike, April - May 1964 - Clippings [folder 1 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 10a)
    Wall Street Journal Chicago Tribune
  - Strike, April - May 1964 - Clippings [folder 2 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 10b)
    Chicago's American Chicago Daily News
  - Strike, April - May 1964 - Clippings [folder 3 of 3] (Box 14, Folder 10c)
    Chicago Daily News Chicago Sun-Times
  - Strike, April - May 1964 - Clippings, part 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Strike, averted, April 1967 - BRT Dismissal of Flagmen on Passenger Trains (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, ICRR's request for an injunction, newspaper clippings
  - Strike, April 1969 - BRT (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Strike, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - System Cooperative Agreement (proposed), 1930 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    among standard railway labor organizations
  - "This Is Our Problem" Presentation, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Red Scare Era anti-socialism/anti-communism presentation by ICRR management
  - Time Clocks, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Time Slips, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Train Dispatchers, 1910-1917 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Train Dispatchers' Association of America [folder 1 of 2], 1901-1916 (Box 14, Folder 20a)
  - Train Dispatchers' Association of America [folder 2 of 2], 1901-1916 (Box 14, Folder 20b)
  - Transportation Passes, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Receipt and return of, by local committee members, etc.
  - Travel Time, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Union Shop, Request of organizations for, 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Board of Mediation, 1926-1929 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Railroad Labor Board, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Vacations - agreements, 1940-1947 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    for various classes of employees
  - Vacations - agreements, 1921-1945 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vacations - agreements, 1940-1946 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Vacations - agreements, 1941-1947 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Visitors on railroad property [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1965 (Box 15, Folder 8a)
  - Visitors on railroad property [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1965 (Box 15, Folder 8b)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions, 1918-1919 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Suppl. #7
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 1 of 2], 1918-1919 (Box 15, Folder 10a)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 2 of 2], 1918-1919 (Box 15, Folder 10b)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions, 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 1 of 3], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 12a)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 2 of 3], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 12b)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 3 of 3], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 12c)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 1 of 2], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 13a)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 2 of 2], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 13b)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions, 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 1 of 2], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 15a)
  - Wage - Rule, General Order No. 27 re Wages - Rules - Working Conditions [folder 2 of 2], 1918-1920 (Box 15, Folder 15b)
  - Wages - Miscellaneous, 1918-1943 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Wage matters - orders and unions of railway employees [folder 1 of 2], 1934-1936 (Box 16, Folder 2a)
    January 1934 - November 1936
  - Wage matters - orders and unions of railway employees [folder 2 of 2], 1934-1936 (Box 16, Folder 2b)
  - Wage matters - orders and unions of railway employees [folder 1 of 2], 1936-1940 (Box 16, Folder 3a)
    December 1936 - November 1940